(Howard:)Sheldon, these look great.
(Sheldon:)l mean,
they're like magnificent little crowns...
(Howard:)...to hang
over my magnificent little jewels.
How did you get them so shiny?
Oh, I buffed them with Turtle wax.
(Sheldon:)The man down at Pep Boys
says from now on...
(Sheldon:)...the urine should just bead up
and roll right off.
(Howard:)Way to go the extra mile.
Your Mee-Maw would be proud.
(Sheldon:)My Mee-Maw
must never know of this.
(Sheldon:)Now will you give
Professor Hawking my paper?
(Howard:)Oh, my dear boy, no. Okay.
(Howard:)Next, this is a sexy French maid
costume I bought for Bernadette.
l thought it might spice things up...
(Howard:)...and get her to dust my room
at the same time, heh...
(Howard:)...but I was wrong and really wrong.
(Sheldon:)You want me to return it for you?